[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Marlon Brandos appointed spokesperson at the 1973 Academy Awards who went on stage to refuse his Best Actor Oscar citing Hollywoods misrepresentation of Native Americans?", "correct_answer": "Sacheen Littlefeather", "incorrect_answers": ["Princess Summer-Fall-Winter-Spring", "Sacajewea", "John Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The character, portrayed by Didi Conn in the movie Grease, was nicknamed Frenchie for what reason?", "correct_answer": "She can french-inhale", "incorrect_answers": ["She has seen the Eiffel Tower", "She was born in Paris", "She studies French"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The endocrine system is made up of glands. Aden(o) means glands; adren(o) means the adrenal glands. What term means enlargement of the adrenal glands?", "correct_answer": "Adrenomegaly", "incorrect_answers": ["Adrenalitis", "Adrenotoxin", "Adrenopathy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the  prefix milli mean?", "correct_answer": "1/1000", "incorrect_answers": ["1000", "1/100000", "1/100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the 13 zodiac constellations, which one is the only constellation not counted as an astrological sign?", "correct_answer": "Ophiucus", "incorrect_answers": ["Platismouis", "There are only 12 zodiac constellations", "Permille"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the word diamond literally mean?", "correct_answer": "Unbreakable", "incorrect_answers": ["Magical", "Stone", "Light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these men has not written a book about Bigfoot/Sasquatch?", "correct_answer": "Lawrence Hayden", "incorrect_answers": ["Grover Kranz", "Jeff Meldrum", "Peter Byrne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elephants intertwine their trunks with the trunks of other elephants, much like a handshake. What does an elephant not do with its trunk?", "correct_answer": "drink through it like through a straw", "incorrect_answers": ["caress a baby elephant", "place food in their mouth", "grab enemies and fling them away"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the male leading role in Mosquito Coast, the last movie in which Butterfly McQueen starred?", "correct_answer": "Harrison Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["Sean Connnery", "Brad Affleck", "Matt Damon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Altmans film The Player was nominated for three Academy Awards. How many awards did it win?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "1", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does WALL-E use to escape the cell in Diagnostics?", "correct_answer": "Laser beam", "incorrect_answers": ["Fire extinguisher", "Nothing. He escapes with the other robots during a power failure.", "Lighter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This aircraft, introduced in 1956, is the main transport plane used by the United States Military.", "correct_answer": "C-130", "incorrect_answers": ["Boeing 777", "Citation X", "Gulf Stream G5"]}]